(street music plays)
- (Man in New York accent)
Here you go, free money.
What's the money?
Buy your boyfriend something nice
Watch the lady. Watch the lady.
Where's it at? Watch it now. Watch it.
- (Women) I'm watching.
- (Man) There it is, make it easy for you.
Point to the one. Remember it, lady.
- (Woman) There.
- Turn it over, Turn it over.
You lose again.
- Why do I keep losing?
- (Crowd) This is the one.
- (Man) You get lucky.
You're learning the game.
Learning the game, learning the game.
(crowd talking)
- I liked you babe. Tell
you what I'm gonna do.
I'll give you a chance to
win all your money back.
Would you like that, huh?
You gotta put a little something.
How 'bout that chain.
Get that chain. Give me the chain
- (crowd talking)
- I'll trade everything in for the chain.
Everything we got here.
This is it. I can feel it.
- (crowd talking)
- (Man) The cards are with
you. The cards are with you.
Yes, that's right. Now
we're playing some cards.
Here we go. Here we go.
Now we're gonna play some cards.
Let's go, let's go. Line 'em up.
Mix 'em up, mix 'em up.
Here we go. Here we go. Here we go.
Right here. Right here.
Here we go.
(fist bangs on table)
- You lose again.
(crowd sighs)
- (Woman) I lost my chain.
- Anybody else?
Thanks. Gotta run.
- Hey, wait. Where you
guys going with my chain?
- (Officer) Hey! Hey!
- They took my chain.
- Calm down lady. It's
okay. I'll get. I'll get it.
(futuristic siren plays)
- Hello?
- They took my chain.
- They did what? What'd they do?
- (Woman) They took my gold chain.
- All right, stay right there.
We're coming right now. Right now.
Yo, Jay hit it. Let's go.
(maracas rattling)
♪ This speech is my recital,
I think it's very vital ♪
♪ To rock (a rhyme),
that's right (on time) ♪
♪ It's Tricky is the title, here we go ♪
♪ It's tricky to rock a rhyme ♪
♪ To rock a rhyme that's right on time ♪
♪ It's tricky ♪
♪ It's tricky (tricky) tricky (tricky) ♪
♪ It's tricky to rock a rhyme ♪
♪ To rock a rhyme that's right on time ♪
♪ It's tricky ♪
♪ Tr-Tr-Tr-Tricky (tricky) Trrrrrricky ♪
♪ I met this little girlie,
her hair was kinda curly ♪
♪ Went to her house and bust her out ♪
♪ I had to leave real early ♪
♪ These girls are really sleazy ♪
♪ All they just say is please me ♪
♪ Or spend some time and rock a rhyme ♪
♪ I said "It's not that easy" ♪
♪ It's tricky to rock a rhyme ♪
♪ To rock a rhyme that's right on time ♪
♪ It's tricky (How is it D?) ♪
♪ It's tricky (tricky)
tricky (trrrricky) ♪
♪ It's tricky to rock a rhyme ♪
♪ To rock a rhyme that's right on time ♪
♪ It's tricky ♪
♪ Tricky (tricky) tricky ♪
♪ In New York the people talk
and try to make us rhyme ♪
♪ They really hawk but we just
walk because we have no time ♪
♪ And in the city it's a
pity cus we just can't hide ♪
♪ Tinted windows don't mean
nothin', they know who's inside ♪
♪ It's tricky to rock a rhyme ♪
♪ To rock a rhyme that's right on time ♪
♪ It's tricky ♪
♪ (How is it D?) Tricky
(tricky) tricky (tricky) ♪
♪ It's tricky to rock a rhyme ♪
♪ To rock a rhyme that's right on time ♪
♪ It's tricky ♪
♪ Tricky (tricky) tricky (tricky) huh ♪
- Excuse me, sir.
Now you've taken all our money,
could you at least teach me
and my little friends
through the marketable skill.
I mean, could 'ya teach us to dance?
- Not with this gim mans.
It's, it's not gonna work.
- Please.
- Uh-uh.
- Please
♪ When I wake up people take
up mostly all of my time ♪
♪ I'm not singin', phone keep
ringin' cus I make up a rhyme ♪
♪ I'm not braggin', people naggin'
cus they think I'm a star ♪
♪ Always tearin' what I'm wearin' ♪
♪ I think they're goin' too far ♪
♪ A girl named Carol follows
Daryll every gig we play ♪
♪ Then D dissed her and dismissed
her, now she's jockin' Jay ♪
♪ I ain't lyin', girls
be cryin' cus I'm on TV ♪
♪ They even bother my poor
father cus he's down with me ♪
♪ It's tricky to rock a rhyme ♪
♪ To rock a rhyme that's right on time ♪
♪ It's tricky ♪
♪ (How is it?) tricky
(tricky) tricky (tricky) ♪
♪ It's tricky to rock a rhyme ♪
♪ To rock a rhyme that's right on time ♪
♪ It's tricky ♪
♪ Tr-Tr-Tr-Tr-Tr-Tricky
(tr-tr-tr-tricky) tr-tr-tr- ♪
♪ We are not thugs (we don't use drugs) ♪
♪ But you assume (on your own) ♪
♪ They offer coke (and lots of dope) ♪
♪ But we just leave it alone ♪
♪ It's like that y'all
(y'all), but we don't quit ♪
♪ You keep on (rock!) shock! ♪
♪ Cus this is it ♪
(helicopter blades whirling)
(crowd cheering)
- Yo, Lee. What's up man? I'm Run-D.M.C.
Ready to rock the house.
- Run D.M.C.?
No, No.
No music.
On stage.
You no Run D.M.C.
No, no.
(crowd cheering)
(feet stomping on stage)
♪ Here we go. It's
tricky to rock a rhyme ♪
♪ To rock a rhyme that's right on time ♪
♪ It's tricky ♪
♪ Tricky, tricky ♪
♪ Tricky, whoa ♪
(crowd cheering)
- And that's tricky man.